&gt;&gt; Hello and welcome to the
&gt;&gt; 大家好 欢迎来到
Enabling Your App for CarPlay
让你的 app 适用于  CarPlay
session.
这个讲座
My name is Albert and I'm an
我的名字是  Albert
engineer on the CarPlay team.
我是  CarPlay  团队中的一名工程师
Today we'll be going through an
今天 我们将简要介绍
overview of how apps behave in
app 在  CarPlay  中是怎样运行的
CarPlay, how to get your app
怎样将你的 app 与
integrated on the CarPlay
CarPlay  平台相结合
platform and best practices and
在开发中比较规范的做法
pitfalls to avoid.
以及常见的错误
Let's look at how apps run in
我们来看一下 app 在  CarPlay  中是
CarPlay.
怎样运作的
When CarPlay is active some
当  CarPlay  运行的时候
information will be available
CarPlay  的屏幕上
and accessible from the CarPlay
会显示
screen.
一些信息
If an app has posted now playing
如果一个 app 给出了关于“正在播放”的元数据
metadata and playback controls
以及音频播放控制
for audio content this
这些信息也会在
information will also be
CarPlay  的主屏幕
accessible from the Now Playing
“正在播放”的
app on the CarPlay Home screen.
app 中显示
Audio will be played through a
音频会通过车上的
car speaker system and some
扩音器系统播放
SiriKit intents will be
CarPlay  支持一些
supported in CarPlay.
SiriKit  框架中的意图
If we user triggers of SiriKit
如果用户触发了一个  CarPlay  不支持的
intent that is not supported
SiriKit  中的意图
while in CarPlay Siri will
Siri  会告诉用户
notify the user that it is not
这个功能
available in the car.
在车中不支持
Even though your app may not
即使你的 app 不支持  CarPlay
support CarPlay users may use
用户也可以处在  CarPlay  系统中时
your app while in CarPlay before
在开始驾驶前
they begin driving.
使用你的 app
To ensure a great user
为了保证一个良好的
experience for all apps in
用户体验
CarPlay make sure that your app
除非收到请求
doesn't play audio unless
否则确保你的 app 不播放音频
requested since your app could
因为你的 app 播放的音频
override currently playing audio
可能会与用户当前
the user intended to play.
想要所播放的内容交叠
In some instances, your app will
在一些情况下
want to interact with other
你的 app 可能会与其他音频
audio streams appropriately.
进行适当的互动
For spoken audio apps such as
对于一些例如有声书籍这种
Audiobooks use this protocol so
播放音频的 app 使用这个协议
your audio will pause when other
让你的声频在其他声频
audio streams are active.
播放的时候暂停
For navigation apps where
对于不时发出指示的
guidance instructions are given
导航的 app
intermittently use these two
使用这两个协议
protocols, the latter of which
第二个协议将会在开始你的音频对话之前
will pause audio streams marked
暂停标为
as spoken audio before
“spoken audio” 的音频
initiating your audio session.
的播放
Because guidance voices will mix
因为你的导航音频将会
with other audio streams set
与其他音频混合播放
your audio session to mixable so
将你的音频对话标为“可以混合”
that it can interact with other
以便与其他音频
audio streams.
互动
For apps that have deeper
那些与  CarPlay
CarPlay integration the app icon
结合程度高的那些 app
will appear on the CarPlay Home
会显示在  CarPlay  的
screen.
主页面
Apps that are launched in
在  CarPlay  中
CarPlay will launch in the
运行的 app
foreground on both the CarPlay
会在  CarPlay  和
and iPhone screen.
iPhone  的屏幕上显示
For apps that are not integrated
对于没有结合  CarPlay  的 app
with CarPlay only the iPhone
只有  iPhone  屏幕上
screen will have the app in the
会显示这个 app
foreground and CarPlay will only
CarPlay  屏幕上
display the Home screen.
只显示主页面
There are certain categories of
有一些种类的 app
apps that can support deeper
可以支持
CarPlay integration.
与  CarPlay  的高度结合
These are audio apps, messaging
这些包括音频 app 短信
and VoIP apps and automaker
语音通话以及汽车生产商的
apps.
app
Audio apps deliver music, news,
音频 app 可以播放音乐 新闻
podcasts and other audio content
播客以及其他音频内容
using a consistent design that's
并且要遵循一定的设计理念
optimized for use in the car.
即适合在车中使用
Messaging and VoIP apps work
采用  Siri  的短信和语音通话 app
using Siri and can be updated to
可以经过升级
appear in CarPlay.
适用于  CarPlay
Automaker apps provide vehicle
汽车生产商的 app
specific controls and displays
可以有特定的汽车控制及显示的功能
to keep drivers connected
让驾驶者使用这些功能时
without leaving CarPlay.
不必离开  CarPlay  的环境
If you think your audio,
如果你认为你的短信 语音通话
automaker, messaging or VoIP
或汽车生产商的 app
calling app has the potential to
有可能支持  CarPlay
be supported by CarPlay tell us
请在  CarPlay
about it at the CarPlay
开发者页面
developer portal.
告诉我们
There you'll be able to request
在那里你可以为你的 app
an entitlement to get your app
申请权限
running in CarPlay.
以便与  CarPlay  结合
Keep in mind that certain assets
不要忘记一些内容和图像
and images will need to have
需要为  CarPlay  特制
CarPlay specific assets and to
图像要  2-3  倍大
provide 2X and 3X sized images
因为根据不同车的
since the CarPlay screen has
屏幕规格
varying resolutions and sizes
CarPlay  的屏幕有
depending on a vehicle's
不同的大小
display.
和分辨率
For more guidance on icons and
关于图标和  CarPlay
designing your app for CarPlay
app 设计的更多信息
check out the iOS Human
请参照  iOS Human Interface Guidelines
Interface Guidelines and the
以及
CarPlay Human Interface
CarPlay Human Interface
Guidelines.
Guidelines
While you can test the CarPlay
你可以用  Xcode  中的  iOS  模拟器
app on iOS simulator in Xcode it
测试  CarPlay  的 app
is best to test on an actual
但是为达到最好的
device connected to a real
真实的测试效果
vehicle head unit for realistic
最好连接真正的设备
results.
在车中测试
For apps that will play audio
对于播放音频的 app
the simulator has some
模拟器在播放状态下
limitations on playback state
有一些局限
which does not reflect on what a
不能反映
user will actually experience.
真正的用户体验
To fully debug your app with
为了用  LLDB  全面调试你的 app
LLDB support Xcode now supports
Xcode  现在支持无线调试
wireless debugging so that an
在调试你的 app
iPhone can be connected to a
的过程中  iPhone
vehicle or aftermarket head unit
可以连接在车上
while debugging your app.
或是车配件上
For more information, please see
更多信息
the debugging with Xcode 9
请参照这一周  WWDC  中
session which will be available
“Xcode  9  调试程序”
this week in WWDC.
这一讲座
If your app uses data protection
如果你的 app
for user data or content keep in
对用户数据使用数据保护
mind that apps in CarPlay will
不要忘记  CarPlay  可能是在
likely run while the iPhone is
iPhone  被密码锁住的
pass code locked.
状态下运行
If your app has pass code
如果你的 app 有密码保护的数据
protected data using the
对文件
following types for files,
钥匙串
keychains or SQL like databases
或  SQL  数据库使用了以下的类别
shown here your data may be
你的数据可能
unavailable while in CarPlay and
在  CarPlay  中无法使用
your app may behave
你的 app 可能会有
unexpectedly.
异常的表现
Let's take a closer look at
让我们仔细的看一下
getting your app integrated with
怎样让你的 app
CarPlay.
与  CarPlay  相结合
We will highlight the three
我们重点举出了三类
categories of apps that support
支持  CarPlay  集成
CarPlay integration, audio apps,
音频 app
messaging and VoIP apps, and
短讯和语音通话
automaker apps.
以及汽车生产商的 app
Let's get started with audio
让我们从音频 app
apps.
开始
Audio apps in CarPlay present
在  CarPlay  中
content in an interface that's
音频 app 的用户界面
optimized for the platform
根据平台而优化
providing the user an easily
为用户提供一个
navigable way to access their
很容易使用的操作系统
content.
便于获得他们想得到的内容
Audio app developers provide a
音频 app 的开发者
data source, as well as a
提供数据来源
navigation hierarchy for the
和导航操作的框架
CarPlay platform to render
以便  CarPlay  的平台
onscreen.
在屏幕上显示
In addition, now playing
另外 “正在播放” 的信息
information will be presented
会显示给用户
providing the user with relevant
相关的元数据
metadata, as well as adjustable
以及一些可以调节的操作选项
commands for the user to handle
以便用户操纵播放速度 播放曲目
playback speeds, tracks and
和其他的一些
other actions audio apps may
音频 app 可能支持的
support.
选项
After receiving the app
app 在获得  CarPlay
entitlement audio apps in
的权限之后
CarPlay must at a minimum
CarPlay  必须至少实现  MP
implement the MP playable
可播放的  API
content APIs, which include the
包括数据来源
data source and delegate in
和委托
order for CarPlay to fetch
这样  CarPlay  才能
content items and initialize
获取内容
playback.
和开始播放
Audio apps must also respond to
音频的 app 必须响应
MPRemoteCommandCenter events
MPRemoteCommandCenter  事件
which let the user perform
让用户对你的内容发送指令
commands on your content, such
例如播放 暂停
as play, pause or skip tracks.
或跳过曲目
Finally, audio apps must set and
最后 音频 app 必须
update the
设定和更新
MPNowPlayingInfoCenter
MPNowPlayingInfoCenter  字典
dictionary which contain
这其中包括
metadata on the item that is
正在播放曲目的元数据
currently playing, such as item
例如
title, artist name or duration
艺术家名称
time.
和时长
Let's take a closer look at how
让我们看一下
data is structured for audio
音频 app 的
apps.
数据结构
CarPlay will ask for content
CarPlay  会使用  NSIndexPath
items at a specific index path
根据特定的路径
using an NSIndexPath.
来找寻内容
And this is different than how
这与  UITableView  中
NSIndexPath objects are used in
NSIndexPath  的使用
UITableView.
有所不同
Let's go through an example
让我们来看一个例子
shown here where the left most
这个例子中最左边的内容
content items are the root items
是根数据项
and can be represented in the
在用户界面中
user interface as individual
可以用单个的窗口
tabs or a root table view.
或者是根子表的形式来体现
Here's the index paths for each
这里是在整个数据结构中
content item represented in the
每个内容的
hierarchy.
路径
When CarPlay asks for a content
当  CarPlay  根据某个路径目录
item for a particular index path
要求某个内容的时候
we, the audio app, would
音频的 app 会
traverse the hierarchy for the
遍历整个结构
requested content item.
来查找所需的内容
In this example, we are asking
在这个例子里
for the first child of the first
我们要求第一个内容下面的第一个元素
content which is the running
也就是 “Running”
playlist content item.
这个播放列表
CarPlay will also ask for the
CarPlay  还会询问某一个目录下面
number of child items of a
包含的子元素的
particular index.
数量
In this example, we are asking
在这个例子里 我们询问
for the number of child items
第二个内容下的
for the third child item of the
第三级中的
second route content item.
子元素数量
In this example, we will return
在这个例子中
two.
数量是 2
Some vehicles may enforce
一些车型可能会根据车辆
limited content to show onscreen
是否在行驶状态
depending on whether the vehicle
而限制屏幕上
is in motion.
可显示的内容
This can limit the number of
这可能会限制屏幕上
rows shown onscreen, as well as
可显示的的行数
container depth when drilling
以及点击进某一个目录后
into content.
可显示的内容
Your app can take these changes
你的 app 可以利用
into account using MP Playable
MPPlayableContentManager
Content Manager.
来处理这些变化
To check if content limits are
查询所显示的内容是否会受到限制
enforced implement the Delegate
使用
Callback Content Manager Did
DelegateCallbackContentManagerDidUpdate
Update and check if the content
来查询内容
limits are enforced.
是否会受限
From there your app can check
用这种方法 你的 app 可以
the context properties to
查询环境属性
determine how many items are
就可以知道
permitted in the table view and
表格视图中
the maximum depth in the
允许多少项内容
hierarchy your app is permitted
以及你的 app 最多可以
to show.
显示几层菜单
If your app benefits from
如果你的 app
displaying data using tabs
更适合页面
rather than exclusively table
而不是表格视图
views you can add tabs by adding
你可以通过将
UI browsable content support
UIBrowsableContentSupportSectionBrowsing
section browsing in your app's
加到的你属性列表中
info.plist file.
来增加页面
We recommend having at most four
我们推荐最多使用  4  个页面
tabs with short titles due to
并使用短的标题
space constraints and for
因为视窗的空间有限
vehicles that have a narrow
并且有些汽车的屏幕比较窄
screen size, as well as
而且在播放内容的同时
accounting for the Now Playing
还需显示
button shown while content is
“正在播放”的
playing.
按钮
Tab image assets will be
页面的图像会在
rendered as template images on
CarPlay  的屏幕上
the CarPlay screen.
做为模版图像显示
Now let's talk about the Now
让我们看一下  CarPlay  中
Playing screen in CarPlay.
“正在播放” 的屏幕
Some controls and metadata here
一些控制选项和元数据
are identical to what is shown
与控制中心中显示的
in Control Center.
是一样的
In general, what controls and
总的来说
data you see in Control Center
你在控制中心中所看到的选项与数据
should also be presented here in
在  CarPlay  的 “正在播放” 屏幕中
the CarPlay Now Playing screen.
也应该有所显示
This Now Playing screen can be
要调出这个“正在播放”的屏幕
accessed either by the user
用户可以点击你
tapping Now Playing on the top
app 视图右上角的
right of your app's navigation
“正在播放”
interface or through the Now
或通过点击  CarPlay  主页面上的
screen.
app 图标
Your app's name will appear on
运行过程中 你的  app  的名字会显示在
the top right of the Now Playing
“正在播放” 的屏幕
screen when it is active.
的右上方
Now Playing screen is the same
“正在播放” 屏幕的元数据
as Control Center and other
与设置控制中心等
sources.
相同
Set a dictionary of information
在 MPNowPlayingInfoCenter 中
to MPNowPlayingInfoCenter and
设置一个信息字典
fill out as much of the entries
提供尽可能多的
as appropriate.
信息
In addition, respond to playback
另外 对播放指令做出回应
commands so that the user can
这样用户可以对内容做出调整
choose to adjust content such as
例如播放 暂停
play, pause, skip tracks or
跳过曲目
shuffle and repeat of playback
随机播放或重复播放
queue.
歌单
These commands here are the ones
这些是 CarPlay
that are supported on the
“正在播放” 的界面
CarPlay Now Playing screen.
支持的指令
New in iOS 11 is the ability to
在新的 iSO 11 中
adjust and display the playback
“正在播放” 的界面支持显示
rate in the Now Playing screen.
和调整播放速度
To display playback rate in your
在  CarPlay  里
app's Now Playing screen in
要想在你的 app 中“正在播放” 的界面里
CarPlay add MPNowPlayingInfo
显示播放的速度
PropertyDefaultPlaybackRate to
需要将  MPNowPlayingInfo PropertyDefaultPlaybackRate
MP Now Playing Info Center and
加到  MP Now Playing Info Center  里
respond to the change playback
并且利用  MPRemoteCommandCenter  里
rate command with an array of
存有所支持的一系列的播放速度的数组
supported rates in
来对调整播放速度的指令
MPRemoteCommandCenter.
做出反应
Here is an example of how you
这里有一个代码的例子
would implement playback rate
展示了怎样实现
adjustments and code.
调整播放速度
In this sample, the default
在这个例子中
playback rate of the currently
默认的当前曲目的播放速度为 x1
playing item is 1.0 and the
支持的
supported playback rates here
播放速度有
are 0.5, 1.0, 1.5, and 2.0.
0.5 1.0 1.5  和  2.0
When the user wants to adjust
若用户想要调整播放速度
the playback speed increment the
当播放速度不断增加 当增加至
playback rate forward cycling
所支持的最快播放速度时
back to the beginning if the
播放速度
audio is playing at the fastest
会循环到
supported rate.
最小值
In this code sample, playback
在这个例子里
rate will increment to 1.5 then
播放速度会增加到 1.5
2.0 and then back to 0.5.
然后到  2.0  然后回到  0.5
Some audio apps may respond to
一些音频 app 会响应
multiple commands in MP Remote
MP  遥控指令中心中的
Command Center.
多项指令
Depending on what commands are
根据指令的不同
enabled CarPlay's Now Playing
运行中的  CarPlay  “正在播放”界面
screen will combine certain
将会结合响应的指令
relevant commands into a single
转化为一个按钮
button such as an ellipsis or a
例如省略号
menu button replacing the
或一个菜单按钮来替代
previous track button.
之前的按钮
For best practices, make sure
规范的做法
that content is actually ready
在调用  MP playable content data source
to be played or be displayed
和 MP playable content
before calling the completion
委托中的
handlers in MP playable content
完成指针之前
data source and MP playable
将要播放的内容
content delegate.
准备好
For apps that do not opt into
对于那些不用页面
tabs and only use table views
只用表格视图的 app
the root table view must return
根表格必须返回
at least one item.
至少一项内容
CarPlay would show a loading
CarPlay  会显示一个
activity indicator and will time
读取任务进行情况的指示
out after period of time if an
如果 app 在一定时限内
app has not responded with
没有返回内容
content.
就会超时
If your app has some initial
如果你的 app 需要一些初始的设置
setup such as login credentials
比如登入的信息
populate the first row with an
在页面的第一行
item informing the user of the
应该提示用户
app's current state onscreen.
app  当前的状态
That's it for enabling audio
关于使用音频的  app  就是这些内容
apps and I'll hand it off to
下面  Chris Whitney  将会讨论
Chris Whitney to discuss
CarPlay  中
messaging and VoIP apps in
有关短息
CarPlay.
和语音通话的 app
&gt;&gt; Hi, I'm Chris Whitney from
&gt;&gt; 大家好 我是  Chris Whitney
the CarPlay engineering team.
来自  CarPlay  工程师团队
Albert talked about audio apps
Albert  谈到了关于使用音频的  app
now I will discuss a few more
下面我会讲解一些其他类别的
categories of apps that can
可以与  CarPlay
integrate with CarPlay.
相结合的  app
The first category I will cover
我要讲解的第一类
is messaging and voice over
是短信
Internet protocol calling apps.
以及用网络协议传输语音的打电话的 app
In CarPlay Siri provides the
在 CarPlay 中  Siri  为
interface for messaging and VoIP
短信以及语音通话  app
calling apps.
提供接口
After the app icon is selected
在主页面上
on the Home screen, Siri offers
当  app  的图标被选中后
interactions for reading
Siri  提供读信息 建立新信息
messages, starting a new message
或开始语音通话
or starting an audio call.
这几种选择
Apps using SiriKit can already
使用了  SiriKit  的  app  已经可以支持这些互动
handle these actions, but the
但对  Siri  发出的
Siri request must contain the
请求中必须包含
app's name.
app  的名字
With a few additional changes
经过一些改动
messaging and VoIP apps can have
短信和语音通话的  app  在  CarPlay  中
a CarPlay experience that
可以包含一个主页面的图标
includes a Home screen icon,
提示
notifications, and a dedicated
以及一个专门的
Siri interface.
Siri  接口
Here are the requirements for an
这里是  CarPlay  中
app to support messaging or VoIP
支持短信和语音通信的  app
calling in CarPlay.
所要满足的要求
Messaging apps must implement
app 必须使用
SirKit messaging intents and
SiriKit  中的短讯意图
sign their app with an
并有专门针对
entitlement that is specific to
CarPlay  短讯的
CarPlay messaging.
授权
Similarly, VoIP calling apps
同样的 语音通话 app
must implement the SiriKit
必须使用
calling intents and sign their
SiriKit  中的通话意图
app with an entitlement that is
并有专门针对
specific to CarPlay VoIP
CarPlay  语音通讯的
calling.
授权
VoIP calling apps must also
语音通话  app  还必须使用
implement CallKit to inform
CallKit 来通知
CarPlay about the status of
CarPlay  通话的
calls.
状态
A single app can support both
一个  app  在  CarPlay  中
messaging and VoIP calling in
可以同时支持短信
CarPlay.
和语音通话
Let's look into the SiriKit
让我们看一下更多
requirements in more detail.
关于  SiriKit  技术要求的细节
For messaging apps, Siri sends
对于短信  app
messages using
Siri  通过
INSendMessageIntent.
INSendMessageIntent  发送信息
Siri reads new incoming messages
Siri  通过  INSearchforMessagesIntent
and searches for unread messages
读取新收到的信息
using INSearchforMessagesIntent.
并搜寻未读信息
And once done reading Siri marks
读信息的过程完成后
messages as read by calling
Siri  通过调用  INSendMessageAttributeIntent
INSendMessageAttributeIntent.
将信息标记为已读
All three intents are required
这三个意图在  CarPlay  中
to support a complete messaging
是支持一个完整的信息读取过程
workflow in CarPlay.
所必须用到的
For VoIP calling apps, Siri
对于语音通话  app
starts audio calls using
Siri  通过调用  INStartAudiCallIntent
INStartAudiCallIntent and
来开始通话
performs searches, such as for
关于搜索 例如搜索未接来电
missed calls using
则通过调用
INSearchCallHistoryIntent.
INSearchCallHistoryIntent
Both intents are required to
这些意图是在  CarPlay  中
support a complete calling
完成一个通话流程
workflow in CarPlay.
所必备的
For details on SirKit see the
关于  SirKit  的细节
session's What's New in SiriKit
请参见“SiriKit  最新更新”
and Making Great SiriKit
以及“创造最好的
Experiences.
SiriKit  体验”
Any app that has already
任何已经使用了  CallKit  的  app
implemented CallKit gets a
都有一个  CarPlay  的接口
CarPlay interface for incoming
用来处理新来电以及
and active calls.
正在通话中的来电
But if your VoIP calling app
但如果你的语音通话  app
hasn't implemented CallKit yet
还没有使用  CallKit
that will be a requirement for
这样是结合  CarPlay
CarPlay integration.
所必须的一个要求
As a general overview, the app
总体来说  app  必须
must report incoming calls to
在接到来电时通知  CallKit
CallKit and handle the start,
来处理开始
answer and end call actions.
接听和挂断的行为
Additional actions, such as
如果该  app  的语音通话平台支持其他行为
mute, grouping, holding and
例如无声 群组
keypad tones should be handled
来电等待和键盘声音
if supported by the app's VoIP
那么这些活动也应该
platform.
在  app  中实现
For more details on CallKit
关于  CallKit  的更多信息
watch the enhancing VoIP apps
请观看  2016  WWDC
with CallKit video from WWDC
“用  CallKit  提高语音通话 app”
2016.
的视频
Apps can show notifications in
app  可以在  CarPlay  中
CarPlay for incoming messages
显示新信息
and missed calls.
和未接来电的提示
There's some additional setup
在  CarPlay  中显示提示
required to show notifications
需要一些
in CarPlay.
其他的设置
The CarPlay option must be
在请求提示通知授权的时候
included when requesting
CarPlay  必须
authorization for notifications
包含在其中
and the messages must be
并且信息必须单独在一个提示的类别中
separated into a notification
通过  CarPlay  选项中
category created with the Allow
允许这个选项
in CarPlay option.
来实现
This notifications category must
提示这个类别
be used exclusively for messages
仅限使用于信息
and it should not include
不应该
notifications for other app
用于其他
features.
app 提示信息
The notification category must
提示这个类别必须指定一个
specify a SiriKit intent to
SiriKit  的意图
handle selection of the
来处理  CarPlay  中的
notification in CarPlay.
对提示的选择
Only messaging or VoIP calling
只满足  CarPlay  的短信
apps that meet the CarPlay
或语音通话的  app
requirements will be allowed to
才会被允许
request authorization for
请求发出
showing notifications.
显示通知的授权
Also, users can use the Settings
同时 用户可以使用设置选项
op to disable showing your app's
来禁止你的  app
notifications in CarPlay.
在  CarPlay  中显示提示通知
Let's look at the code for
让我们看一下  CarPlay  中
setting up notifications in
设置通知的
CarPlay.
代码
First, include the CarPlay
首先 在请求发送提示通知的授权时
option when requesting
将  CarPlay  选项
authorization for notifications.
包含进去
Gracefully disable notifications
如果用户不接受提示通知
related features if the user
则让你的 app 恰当地禁止
declines notification
与发送提示
authorization.
有关的功能
Next, create a new message
接下来 建立一个新的信息类别
category that contains only
仅包含关于
notifications for messages.
信息的通知
Notifications for other app
关于其他功能的通知
features, such as news or games
例如新闻或游戏
should not be included in this
不应该被包含在
notification category.
这个通知类别中
Assign an identifier to this
给这个类别加一个标记
category and make sure that any
确保所有本地
local or remote notifications
或远程的
for messages have the same
信息通知提醒
category identifier.
都有同样的类别标记
Set up an intent identifier to
建立一个意图的标记
configure the Siri interaction
以便通知选项在
when the notification is
CarPlay  中被选中时
selected in CarPlay.
来设置  Siri  的互动
Usually that will be
通常使用的是
INSearchForMessages
INSearchForMessagesIntentIdentifier
IntentIdentifier which
这个意图
configures Siri to search for
设置  Siri  让它搜寻这个意图
and then read the message that
并读取与这个提示通知
matches this notification.
对应的信息
There are a few best practices
关于开发短信和语音通话  app
to follow when building
有一些推荐的
messaging and VoIP calling apps.
对应的信息
Notifications should only
在通知的标题或副标题中
include information like the
应该只包含发送者
sender and group name in the
和群组名称
title and subtitle.
等信息
The contents of a message should
信息的内容不应该
not appear in CarPlay.
在  CarPlay  中显示出来
After reading a message, Siri
读取一条信息过后
will use
Siri 将使用
INSentMessageAttributeIntent to
INSentMessageAttributeIntent
mark content as read.
将信息标为已读
The read status should be
读取状态
reflected in the app and
应该显示在 app 中
subsequent search for messages
在之后搜索信息的活动中
requests.
也应该体现
Since users may drive in and out
用户可能驶入或者驶出信号覆盖的范围
of cellular coverage areas apps
所以  app  应该使用提示
should use notifications to
来通知用户
communicate any missed calls or
未接来电
message delivery failures.
或者发送失败的信息
This may require setting up
像我们之前描述的那样
additional notification
这可能需要
categories as we have described
单独设置另一个
earlier.
提示类别
The final category of apps that
可以结合  CarPlay  的
can integrate into CarPlay are
最后一个类别的  app
automaker apps.
是汽车生产商的  app
Automaker apps are the only
只有这类汽车生产商的  app
category of apps that can
可以在  CarPlay  中
display a custom user interface
显示自定义
in CarPlay.
用户界面
In this example, the automaker
在这个例子中
app provides controls for
汽车生产商的  app
adjusting the climate settings,
提供温度设置
selecting radio stations, and
选择收音机频道
summoning roadside assistance.
以及呼叫公路援助的功能
Providing these controls in an
在汽车生产商的  app  中提供这些功能
automaker app allows the user to
让用户可以不必离开  CarPlay
adjust the vehicle's climate and
就可以调节车的温度
radio without leaving CarPlay.
和收音机
Automaker apps can take
汽车生产商的  app  可以
advantage of the iPhone's
利用 iPhone  的
Internet connectivity and
网络连接
powerful development platform to
和强大的开发平台
create additional vehicle
带来更多汽车相关的
features.
功能
For example, this automaker app
例如 这个汽车生产商的 app
could enable Siri driven voice
可以利用Siri
control of the climate and radio
来语音控制温度和收音机
settings.
设置
Automaker apps must be created
汽车生产商的  app
by the car's manufacturer to
必须由汽车制造商来制作
provide information and control
需要车的制造商提供信息
features on a connected vehicle.
来控制汽车上的功能
These apps must be signed with a
这些  app  必须有一个特定的
specific CarPlay protocols
CarPlay  协议的
entitlement.
签名授权
They must display a user
它们必须在  CarPlay  里
interface in CarPlay.
显示一个用户界面
And they must only appear on
并且只能在支持的
supported vehicles.
车型上显示
CarPlay determines if an
CarPlay  通过匹配
automaker app is supported on a
汽车的外部配件协议
given vehicle by matching the
与 app 的
external accessory protocols
CarPlay  协议权限
declared by the vehicle with the
来决定某款车型
CarPlay protocols entitlement
是否支持某个
sign in to the app.
汽车生产商的 app
Thus, it is important to
因此 在汽车开发制造过程中
consider potential automaker
考虑可能的汽车生产商的  app
apps during vehicle development
是很重要的
in order to have the appropriate
这样才能保证
set of protocols declared by the
汽车配有适当的
vehicle.
协议声明
Here's an example of how CarPlay
这个例子展示了  CarPlay  是怎样
matches automaker apps to
将汽车与汽车生产商的 app
vehicles.
相匹配
This vehicle declares two
这个汽车有两个协议的声明
protocols, a performance
一个是表现的协议
protocol for collecting vehicle
用来采集汽车的数据
statistics and a protocol for
还有一个控制温度
climate control.
的协议
As shown here, protocol names
像这儿所显示的那样
should be declared in reverse
协议的名字应该用
DNS format.
反向域名格式
The automaker wants to take
汽车生产商希望
advantage of the vehicle's
在一个新叫做“跑道”的  app  中
performance statistics in a new
利用有关汽车
app called Track Laps that's
表现的数据
designed for use on racetracks.
这个  app  是为了赛道所设计
The app includes the performance
该  app  包含了
protocol and its entitlements
表现协议以及授权
and since both the app and the
并且 app 和车
vehicle support the performance
都支持表现协议
protocol the Track Laps app will
所以 “跑道” 将会
appear in CarPlay.
显示在  CarPlay  中
Automaker apps can also support
汽车生产商的  app
multiple protocols.
还可以支持多个协议
This automaker decides to follow
这个汽车生产商决定
up on the success of Track Laps
在“跑道”这个 app 成功的基础上
with a new app called Comfort
开发一个新的 app
Cruise that conveniently
叫做“舒适旅程”
configures the radio and climate
可以根据驾驶者的喜好
control with the driver's
很方便的
favorite settings for commuting.
调节收音机和温度
The app's entitlements include
这个  app  的授权
both the climate protocol and a
包括一个温度的协议
new radio protocol.
和一个新的收音机的协议
This vehicle doesn't support the
该车不支持收音机的协议
radio protocol, but since both
但因为车辆和  app
the app and the vehicle support
都支持温度协议
the climate protocol the Comfort
“舒适旅程” 这个  app
Cruise app will appear in
将会显示在
CarPlay.
CarPlay  中
After launching automaker apps
在汽车生产商的  app  开始运行之后
should query the supported
应该询问所支持的外部配件协议
external accessory protocols and
并且在用户界面上
only display a user interface
应该只显示
for the supported features.
支持的功能
In this example, the Comfort
在这个例子中
Cruise app should only show
“舒适旅程”这个  app
climate controls since the radio
应该只显示温度控制
protocol is not supported on
因为该车不支持
this vehicle.
收音机协议
The automaker wants to create
这个汽车生产商想开发另外一个  app
another app called Charge Up
叫做“充电”
that shows their electric
来显示他们的
vehicle charging stations.
电动车充电站
To limit this app to only their
为了让这个 app 只适用于他们自己的电动车
electric vehicles the automaker
这个汽车生产商在  app  的权限中
declares a new electric protocol
设定了一个
in the app's entitlements.
新的电子协议
Since this vehicle does not
因为这款车
support the electric protocol
不支持电子协议
the Charge Up app will not
“充电”这个  app
appear in CarPlay on this
将不会显示在
vehicle.
CarPlay  中
Building an automaker app
开发一个汽车生产商的  app
requires communicating with the
需要与该汽车
vehicle.
进行信息交换
Automaker apps must communicate
汽车生产商的  app
directly from the iPhone to the
必须直接通过  iPhone
vehicle using the External
使用“外部配件”框架
Accessory framework.
与车辆进行信息交换
Directly communicating using
直接通过外部配件
External Accessory improves the
进行交流
responsiveness of the app and
提高了 app 的反应速度
avoids relying on connectivity
并避免了
to Internet services.
依赖网络连接
To use the External Accessory
要使用外部配件框架
framework the app should define
app  需要像之前演示的那样
a custom protocol name as shown
定义一个自定义的协议名称
previously, implement the named
在汽车的软件中
protocol in the vehicle
和 app 所检测到的
software, in the app observe
配件连接事件中
accessory connection events, and
应用这个协议
upon connection initialize an EA
在建立连接的时候
session to create networking
初始化一个  EA  对话
streams of the vehicle.
来建立车中的网络传输
For more information see
了解更多信息
External Accessory programming
请参见外部配件编程的
topics.
话题
Automaker apps can use UIKit to
汽车生产商的 app 可以使用  UIKit
display a user interface on the
来在  CarPlay  的屏幕上
CarPlay screen.
显示用户界面
To create an interface in
要创立一个  CarPlay  的接口
CarPlay the app should observe
app  需检测
the UIScreen connection events
UIScreen  连接事件
and when the screen connects
当屏幕建立连接时
verify that the connected
验证连接的屏幕的
screen's traits contain the
特征包含
CarPlay idiom.
CarPlay  的惯用语法
Besides CarPlay, iOS also
除了  CarPlay iOS  还支持
supports other external
其他外部的显示系统
displays, such as an airplane
例如飞机上的
display.
屏幕
Only show CarPlay content on
屏幕只应该显示有  CarPlay  惯用语法的
screens with the CarPlay idiom.
CarPlay  内容
The app creates a UIWindow for
这个 app 在  CarPlay  屏幕上
the CarPlay screen and sets the
建立了一个  UIWindow
root view controller to a custom
将根视图的控制器设置为
UI view controller subclass.
自定义  UI  视图
Let's see how this looks when
控制器的子类
all put together.
让我们看一下这些结合在一起是怎样的
Here's the code for displaying a
这里是在  CarPlay  中
view controller on the CarPlay
显示视图控制器的
screen.
代码
Usually this code would be
通常这些代码或者放在
placed either in your UI
你  UI  程序的委托中
application delegate or in a new
或者放在为这些代码所建的
class you've made for this code.
一个新的类中
First, we'll add a new class
首先 我们加上一个新的类
property to store the UIWindow
来储存我们
that we will create for the
为  CarPlay 所创建的
CarPlay screen.
UIWindow
Next, we'll define an instance
接下来我们定义一个
method called updateCarWindow.
叫做  updateCarWindow  的实例方法
To check if a CarPlay screen is
要检查是否连接了  CarPlay  的屏幕
connected we look for a UIScreen
我们检测含有  CarPlay
that has the CarPlay idiom.
惯用语法的  UIScreen
If no CarPlay idiom screens are
如果没有含  CarPlay  惯用语法的屏幕存在
available then release any
我们就取消
previously created UIWindow
之前建立的任何  UIWindow
since CarPlay may have
因为与  CarPlay  的连接
disconnected.
可能断开了
If a CarPlay screen is connected
如果  CarPlay  屏幕是连接上的
initialize a new UIWindow for
则初始化一个新的  UIWindow
that screen and set up a custom
并建立一个自定义的
rootViewController that contains
rootViewController
the content that should appear
在其中包含要在  CarPlay  中
in CarPlay.
显示的内容
Here we are using a UI view
在这里我们使用
controller subclass called
UI view controller  的一个子类
carViewController.
叫做  carViewController
That class will need to be
这个类需要
implemented.
被实现
Your app may launch after
你的  app  可以在连接  CarPlay
CarPlay connected.
之后启动
To handle that scenario call
为了处理这种情况
updateCarWindow early in your
尽早的在你的 app 中
application's lifecycle, such as
调用  updateCarWindow
an application did finish
例如在完成
launching with options.
启动的选项里
Since CarPlay can also connect
因为  CarPlay  在你的 app 启动过后
after your app is launched
也可以连接
listen for the
检测
UIScreenDidConnect and
UIScreenDidConnect
UIScreenDidDisconnect
和 UIScreenDidDisconnect
notifications and call
通知并调用
UpdateCarWindow in response to
UpdateCarWindow
those events.
来处理这些事件
There are a few differences in
UIKit 在 CarPlay
UIKit behavior on the CarPlay
屏幕中的表现
screen compared to the iPhone's
和在  iPhone  主屏幕中的表现
main screen.
有些不同
UIButtonTypeSystem displays with
UIButtonTypeSystem  以  CarPlay  默认的
the default CarPlay style and is
显示风格来显示
the recommended way to create
也是推荐的创建按钮的方法
buttons since it provides a
因为这样一来它的格式和表现
style and behavior consistent
就会与其他
with other CarPlay apps.
CarPlay app  保持一致
In CarPlay,
在 CarPlay 中
UITableViewController may limit
UITableViewController  可能会
the length of tables and for
限制表格的长度
vehicles with a hardware
对于有导航硬件的车来说
navigation device, such as the
使用
[inaudible], the corresponding
UIFocusEnvironment
focus movements are handled
以及相关的焦点类
through UIFocusEnvironment and
来处理相应的
the related focus classes.
焦点动作
Note that not all system user
注意  UIKit   提供的
interface elements provided by
所有的系统用户界面元素
UIKit are available to automaker
并不是都可以用在汽车制造商的
apps.
app  中
There's a selection of SiriKit
有一些  SiriKit  的意图
intents relevant to automaker
是与汽车制造商的
apps.
app  相关的
The commands intents are
这些意图指令
available to all apps.
对所有  app  开放
They don't require a CarPlay
它们并不需要连接  CarPlay
connection nor participating in
或者是参与到
the CarPlay app program.
一个  CarPlay  的  app  中
But an automaker app is a great
但是汽车生产商的  app
place to implement these
是利用这些意图的一个好地方
intents, which include locking
包括可以锁车
the vehicle, checking the fuel
检查汽油使用情况
level and sounding the horn.
和按响喇叭
There's also a set of intents
还有一系列的意图
that require a CarPlay
需要连接  CarPlay
connection and can only be
而且只能应用在
implemented by automaker apps.
汽车生产商的  app  上
The CarPlay intents include
CarPlay  意图包括控制温度
climate control, defroster and
除霜
seat heater settings.
控制座椅加热
Also included are intents for
还有控制收音机和
tuning the radio and selecting
选择音频来源
an audio source.
的意图
There are a few best practices
汽车生产商  app  的设计
for automaker apps.
有一定的规范
The first is to make your app
首先 要让你的  app
useful even when CarPlay is not
在没有  CarPlay  的情况下
available.
依然可以发挥作用
For example, when disconnected
例如 当断开与  CarPlay  的连接的时候
from CarPlay an automaker app
汽车生产商的  app
can use Internet services to
可以通过连接因特网
remotely communicate with the
来与汽车进行
vehicle.
信息交换
Consider backwards and forwards
在设计汽车生产商  app  的时候
compatibility in your automaker
考虑兼容的
app.
问题
App updates should continue to
app  的更新应该继续支持老款的车型
support older vehicles and new
新的功能
features should not break
不应该影响到
existing versions of the app.
现有的  app  版本
Simplify the user interface,
简化用户界面
most CarPlay apps should only
多数的  CarPlay  app 界面
contain fundamental interface
应该只包括基本的互动元素
elements, such as buttons,
例如按钮
labels, tables, navigation bars
标签 表格 导航条
and tabs.
和页面标签
Finally, if your automaker app
最后 如果你的汽车生产商 app
supports vehicles with a
支持的车型上
hardware navigation device such
有硬件的导航装置
as a [inaudible] determine how
要考虑
focus should move between the UI
怎样将焦点在不同的
elements.
UI  元素中转移
We hope that you've learned how
我们希望你学到了
to integrate an audio,
怎样将一个语音 信息
messaging, VoIP calling or
语音通话或汽车生产商的 app
automaker app into CarPlay.
结合到  CarPlay  中
For more information about
关于  CarPlay  的
CarPlay, see
更多信息
developer.apple.com.
请访问  developer.apple.com
You can also learn more in
你也可以
related sessions.
从相关的讲座中
See the Debugging with Xcode 9
了解更多内容
session for more information
“用  Xcode 9  调试程序”
about debugging apps during a
可以告诉你关于
wired CarPlay connection.
有线连接  CarPlay  调试程序的更多信息
For more information about
关于 SiriKit 的更多信息
SiriKit, see the sessions What's
请参考“ SiriKit  最新更新”
New in SiriKit and Making Great
以及 “创造最好的
SiriKit Experiences.
SiriKit  体验”
To learn how wireless CarPlay
关于  CarPlay  怎样通过无线工作
works watch the Developing
请观看“开发无线  CarPlay  系统”
Wireless CarPlay Systems video.
的视频
Videos from WWDC 2016 are
WWDC 6 的视频
available for both CallKit and
也包括 CallKit 和
CarPlay systems development
CarPlay  系统开发的
topics.
话题